Administrative Committee; Records ua000.006
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Administrative Committee Records
1971-1981
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Administrative Committee
State University of New York at Albany.
ua000.006
1.0 cubic ft.
This collection contains items from a committee created to oversee major budget decisions. Materials include meeting agendas, minutes, and university wide memos about the decisions made at these meetings.
Administrative History
The Administrative Committee was a meeting of the main members of the administration of the University at Albany. This included the President, all Vice Presidents, along with other higher ups in the University. This committee controlled the University budget and all major policy decisions. It was created shortly affter the new University campus was fully opened.
Scope and Contents
This collection is made up of various docuemnts that were created by the Administrative Committee. Items include meeting minutes, correspondence, meeting schedules, and various memos realesed as a result of these meetings. They pertain to major budget decisions covering all University functions inclduing commencement, enrollment growth, and graduate assistants. Most documents include memos sent out to the faculty and staff detailing what was discussed in the meetings and what was decided on.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
All items in this manuscript group were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
Arrangement
Collection is arranged in chronological order.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Universities and colleges--Administration; Universities and colleges--New York (State); Budgets.; College student orientation; College presidents--United States; UAlbany Task Forces & Committees
- Master Plan, Minutes, Memoranda, 1971 September-1971 December (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Master Plan, Enrollment Info, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Memoranda, Minutes, Agenda, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Minutes, Memoranda, 1973 June-1973 December (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Minutes, Memoranda, 1973 January-1973 May (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Records, Minutes, 1974 January-1974 August (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Minutes, Memoranda, 1974 September-1974 December (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Administrative Records, 1975 January-1975 March (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Administrative Records, 1975 April-1975 May (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Administrative Records, 1975 June-1975 August (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Administrative Records, 1975 September-1975 December (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Administrative Records, 1976 January-1976 August (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Agendas, Documentation, 1976 September-1976 December (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Telephone Committee, 1976-1977 February (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Agendas, Documentation, 1977 January-1977 February (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Agendas / Memoranda, 1977 March-1977 August (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Minutes, Memoranda, Documentation, 1977 November-1977 December (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Memoranda, Agenda, Documentation, 1978 September-1979 February (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Minutes, Memoranda, Documentation, 1978 January-1978 August (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Minutes, Memoranda, 1979 March-1980 September (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Minutes, Memoranda, 1980 August-1981 May (Box 1, Folder 21)